-你好啊  弗萊迪  最近怎樣  -挺好
- Hey, Freddy! How ya doing? - Hey.
那就好  你這麼說我就安心了
All right, that's what I like to hear.
-謝了夥計  -改天再聊
- My man. - Catch you later, brother.
副總統夫人的污點
特區日報
翻譯  章魚X
翻譯  某豚
翻譯  衛老哥
翻譯  風吹日落
翻譯  香茗小焙
翻譯  木月
翻譯  小飯
翻譯  喃喃
時間軸  寶寶
後期  餓得慌
特效  寶寶
顧問  老杜
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第二季  第九集
人人影視傾情奉獻
《日報》我能聯繫的人都聯繫了
I spoke to everyone I know at the Daily.
沒人告訴我誰給的照片  但肯定是雷米
Nobody's naming sources, but it has to be Remy.
嘉樂威要出面回應嗎
Is Galloway going on the record?
不會的  他會先和我們接觸
He wouldn't. Not without speaking to us first.
-最好確保這一點  -我這就去和亞當說
- Let's be sure about that. - I'll talk to Adam.
也許避免和他接觸會更好些
Maybe it's smarter to avoid contact.
總得有人出面回應
Somebody has to respond,
不是他就是我們  或者一起回應
whether it's him, or us, or both.
我們得協調好  小心應對
We have to coordinate, and do it carefully.
這事交給我吧
Let me take care of this.
我們先想好了
Well, let's just think this through.
不會有問題的  弗蘭西斯
I've got it covered, Francis.
那好
Ok.
我該怎麼辦  還去辦公室嗎
What should I do? Head back to the office?
我覺得你還是在家辦公比較好
I think you should work here.
你出門的話  很難躲開媒體
We can't avoid the press if you leave.
-那好  你把好門  -好的  先生
- All right. You hold down the fort. - Yes, sir.
你聽克萊爾差遣
And you follow Claire's lead.
這事會解決的  先生
We'll shut this down, sir.
絕不能有差池
There can't be any doubt.
我們再過一遍時間線
Let's walk through a timeline.
-你最初遇見他是什麼時候  -惠特尼雙年展
- So you first met him when? -In Whitney Biennial...
這事傷害了我們兩個人
This hurts us both.
但要著手去處理的人不是我
But it's not my wound to suture.
克萊爾必須親自動手
Claire must be the surgeon.
只有她才能穩住局勢
Only she can stop the bleeding.
裏面有盤子
You know we got them plates in there.
按你要求的改好了
All the changes you asked for.
多給你5%的追補股份
Gave you five more points on the post-recoupment share.
營銷宣傳材料需要你認可
Approval over all the marketing materials.
銀泉旗艦店的人事也要經你認可
Approval over the staff hires of the flagship in Silver Spring.
-接下來做什麼  -簽字就行
- So, what next? - You sign.
-然後我九萬五就到手了  -這週末吧
- And I get my $95,000? - By the end of the week.
得先把錢從主賬戶注入公司賬戶
Just have to wire it from our main account into the LLC,
還得核對賬目
had cash years to check for.
我還想給你看看這個
I want to show you this.
這是醬料瓶的樣品
It's a mockup of the bottle design.
他們已經開始為銀泉店的外觀
And we already started on the concept layouts
進行概念設計了
for the Silver Spring location.
為什麼牆氈都裂開了
Why's that linoleum peeling up?
追求真實感啊
To make it seem real.
我希望比這漂亮些
I wanted it to look nicer than this.
我們可以改掉牆氈的設計
We can scratch the peeling linoleum,
但不想顯得太高端
but we don't want it to look too nice.
你想讓白人有種體驗下層生活的感覺
You want them white folks to feel like they slummin' it.
不  是為了營造地道的氣氛
No, to have an authentic atmosphere.
我就負責扮演黑鬼
And I get to play the nigger.
弗萊迪  你也知道這種事
Look, Freddy, you know how this works.
他們不只是來吃肋排
They don't just want the ribs,
而是要那種體驗
they want the experience,
還不用出市郊
but without having to leave the suburbs for it.
我們又不是賣燭光晚餐的
We're not selling candlelit dinners here.
但我保證
But I promise,
所有決策都會經過你的首肯
nothing gets built without your signing off.
你想讓我怎麼辦
So, what do you want me to do?
-我需要你出面否認  -否認戀情嗎
- I need you to deny it. - The affair?
戀情  照片  所有這一切
The affair, taking the photograph, everything.
我們有公開來往的記錄
We have a public history.
我曾捐獻作品給...
I donated work for your...
你可以說那純粹是業務往來
You can say we had a business relationship,
但你沒有給我拍躺在床上的照片
but that you didn't take the picture of me in the bed.
就說是合成的
It was Photoshopped.
隨便你怎麼說
Whatever it is you need to say.
我很抱歉  克萊爾
I'm so sorry, Claire.
我只印了一版  還在我這兒呢
I only have one print and it's still here.
那個你也得銷毀掉
You have to destroy it.
電子文檔也要刪掉
The digital file also.
但刪之前先發給我們一份
But e-mail us a copy first.
為什麼
Why?
我們得確認照片裏沒有任何痕跡
We need to make sure that there's nothing in the image
能聯繫到你的工作室
that links to your studio.
全都聽你的
Whatever you think is best.
謝謝你  亞當
Thank you, Adam.
我當時在看
I watched you...
你接受CNN直播採訪的時候
...when you did the CNN interview.
我本來打定主意不看的  但沒忍住
I promised myself I wouldn't, but I couldn't help it.
我們要因為這種事才說上話真是遺憾
It's a shame it takes this for us to talk to one another.
除了這事  你還好嗎
You're well, besides this?
嗯  你來過之後
Yeah. I spent three months in Colombia
我去哥倫比亞工作了三個月
after you came up here to work,
其實也是逃避
but also to get away.
我遇到了一個人
I met someone.
她來自波哥大
She's from Bogota.
與當地非政府組織合作
She was working with an NGO there.
叫伊奈茲
Her name's Inez.
我們同居了
She's living with me now.
真是...
That...
進展很快
Things happened quickly.
是啊  確實
Yeah. They did.
我該掛了
I should go.
得到指示前  我不能和媒體接觸
So I won't talk to the press until I get instructions.
對
That's right.
能聽到你的聲音真好
It's good to hear your voice.
我也是
You too.
-打完電話了  -嗯
- You finished? - Yeah.
真是瘋狂
Crazy, right?
海洛因  可卡因  霹靂可卡因
Smack, crack, blow.
不用  謝謝
No, thanks.
來點吧  老頭  我們手裏應有盡有
Come on, old man. We got what you need.
我什麼都不需要
I don't need anything.
想要進門  就得買點
Gotta buy somethin' if you want to get inside.
別擋路
Get out the way.
你說什麼
What?
我認真的
For real.
你他媽的給我滾開
You need to get the fuck on outta my way.
跟你鬧著玩而已  黑鬼
Just fucking with you, nigger.
他媽的冷靜點嘛
Chill the fuck out.
你是誰
Who are you?
你爺爺  開門
Your grandfather. Open up.
你打算怎麼辦
What's your plan?
在家辦公
Work from home.
就不會把鬧劇帶去白宮
You don't need me dragging this circus to the White House.
我是說聲明打算怎麼說
I mean in terms of a statement.
我們正在起草  力求簡短有力
We're drafting one, short and sweet.
抱歉  弗蘭克  但我必須得問
Forgive me, Frank, but you know I have to ask.
如果是真的  我會告訴您的  先生
If it were true, I would tell you, sir.
需要我發表公開聲明嗎
Would you like me to go on record?
說我支持你...
Say I stand beside--
不不  我很感激  總統先生
No, no, no. I appreciate that, Mr. President,
但您不該為這種爛事髒了自己的手
but you shouldn't dirty your hands with this sort of garbage.
如果媒體逼問
If the press corners you,
告訴他們您不會搬弄是非
just tell them you don't engage in gossip mongering.
先生  嘉樂威先生好像要上電視了
Sir, it seems Mr. Galloway is about to appear on television.
去吧  有需要就告訴我
Go. Let me know if there's anything I can do.
謝謝  先生
Thank you, sir.
下午好
Good afternoon.
我沒什麼好說的
I have very little to say.
亞當·嘉樂威  攝影師
針對副總統妻子外洩照片一事作出回應
只有一點  我從沒和克萊爾·安德伍德有過私情
Only that I never had any romantic involvement with Claire Underwood,
也沒有拍攝《特區日報》發表的照片
and that I did not take the photograph printed in the DC Daily.
我對副總統夫婦要面對這種
I'm sorry that the vice president and his wife
荒唐的折磨感到遺憾
have to go through this ridiculous ordeal.
我想請媒體不要把我和未婚妻捲入此事
And I would ask that the media leave both my fiancee and me out of it.
謝謝
Thank you.
一小時內能準備好嗎
You'll be ready in an hour?
嗯  會準備好的
Yes. We'll be ready.
最好換身更...
You might want to change into something more...
-保守的衣服嗎  -對
- Conservative? - Yes.
我先放點口風出去
I'm gonna go throw the hounds a bone.
我知道這很丟人...
I know it's demeaning --
不許再多說
Not another word.
我該更謹慎的
I should have been more careful.
這事就讓它過去吧  就像以前一樣
We'll put this behind us, just like we've always done.
我其實也挺希望
Part of me wishes...
什麼
What?
你會更介意
That you'd be more upset.
塔斯克盯上你的原因是我
Tusk came after you because of me.
你才有資格介意
It's you who should be upset.
浪費精力  對吧
Wasted energy, isn't it?
對我倆來說都是
For both of us.
要排練一下嗎
Shall we rehearse?
我不需要你的幫助
I don't need your help.
這不是施捨
This ain't a handout.
你得慢慢還給我  給我打工
You have to pay me back over time. Work for it.
給你打工
Work for you?
無論如何  我都會拿到房子
I'm gonna get the house either way.
你住不住  那是你的選擇
Whether you choose to live in it is up to you.
是啊  我就需要這個
Yeah, just what I need.
你坐在安樂椅上
You in the easy chair,
每次我進門出門都對我冷嘲熱諷
laying into me every time I come in and out the door.
房子是給你和杜肖恩的
The place is for you and DeShawn.
我住我自己的公寓
I'm gonna be at my own apartment.
你確定那黑鬼不是在騙你嗎
You sure this nigga ain't just sellin' you smoke?
白紙黑字寫在合同里  怎樣都有九萬五
Says it right in the contract, 95 Gs no matter what.
我不確定
I don't know, man.
五年沒見
Five years I don't see you,
現在卻跑過來  說你弄到了九萬五
then you come knocking on the door, talking about you got 95 Gs--
是你的選擇
Your choice.
你不想再讓我去監獄裏探視你
You didn't want me to visit you no more in jail
你出來之後也不想見...
and you sure didn't want to see me after you got out --
我還是不想見你
I still don't want to see you.
我已經站在這裏了
Well, here I am.
滾出去  老傢伙
Get the fuck outta here, old man.
聽我說  孩子
You listen to me, boy.
我一直沒什麼可以給你
I never had nothing to give you.
我沒有錢  我有的你也不想要
I didn't have no money, and you didn't want whatever I had.
但這可是一棟房子
But we talking about a house.
杜肖恩應該住在一個
DeShawn deserves to live better
-比這裏更好的地方  -這不是為了他
- than in a place like this. - This ain't about him.
而是為了你
It's about you.
你知道去哪裏找我
You know where to find me.
再見  孩子
See you, kid.
還有不到30分鐘
Less than 30 minutes.
他們要否認嗎
Are they going to deny?
還是讓副總統和夫人自己來說吧
I'm gonna let the Vice President and his wife speak for themselves.
他們跟嘉樂威先生有聯絡嗎
Have they been in contact with Mr. Galloway?
不  沒有
No, they haven't.
為什麼他們過了一整天才做出回應
Why has it taken them a full day to respond.
我相信你們肯定可以理解
I'm sure you can understand that
他們想先就誹謗與污蔑問題
they wanted to consult with legal counsel first
咨詢法律顧問
regarding defamation and slander.
你是說他們要否認這段婚外情
You're saying they will deny the affair.
我是說他們30分鐘之內就會出來
I'm saying they'll be out here in 30 minutes
你們可以引述他們的話而不是我的
and you can quote them instead of me.
謝謝你們的耐心
Thank you all very much for your patience.
真是恨死這個了
I hate this.
什麼  等待嗎
What, waiting?
不  婚外情  都是狗屁
No, the affair. It's bullshit.
我覺得自己像個小報狗仔
I feel like a tabloid hack.
你寧願整天困在白宮那邊嗎
You'd rather be stuck at the White House all day?
去他的
Fuck this.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
用我的寶貴時間做點有意義的事
To do something meaningful with my time.
你好  幫我訂一張飛往聖路易斯的機票
Hey, I need you to book me a flight to St. Louis.
如果可以的話最好是今晚
Tonight, if you can find something.
沒有問答環節  別費心提問了
No Q&A, so don't even try.
請大家規矩一點
Behave yourselves, people.
竟然有人懷疑
I find it very painful
我對我深愛的丈夫
that anyone would suggest
會有不忠行為
I'm capable of being unfaithful to my husband,
這讓我感到非常痛心
whom I love dearly.
我與亞當·嘉樂威已相識多年
I've known Adam Galloway for years.
我們都認識他很多年了
We both have.
我負責淨水計劃時
When I ran the Clean Water Initiative,
曾委託他為營銷活動
I commissioned him to do a series of photographs
拍攝一系列攝影作品
for the marketing campaign.
而他也極為慷慨地為我們的籌款拍賣會
And he was extremely generous by donating work
捐贈了自己的作品
for our fund-raising auctions.
所以我不知道他為什麼要否認拍攝過這張照片
So I'm not sure why he would deny taking the photograph.
我喜歡亞當的作品  所以讓他拍了這幅肖像
I love Adam's work, so I asked him to take this portrait.
我們在這裏拍的  就在這棟房子裏
We did it here, at the house.
拍攝時弗蘭西斯就在旁邊
Francis was there during the shoot.
這是一份生日禮物
It was a birthday present.
克萊爾問我想要什麼樣的肖像
Claire asked me what sort of portrait I wanted,
我說就拍她睡覺的樣子吧
and I said I want one of her sleeping,
因為她睡著的時候非常美
because she's so very beautiful when she's sleeping.
照片就掛在我二樓的辦公室裏
It hangs in my office on the second floor.
他們在說謊
They're fucking lying.
所以我只能猜測
So I can only assume
亞當被媒體的關注嚇到了
that Adam was intimidated by the media attention,
婚外情傳聞: 副總統與夫人出面回應
所以想撇清關係
and he needed to distance himself.
什麼
What?
但真相其實就是
But really, all we have here
他是一位才華橫溢的攝影師
is a very talented photographer
而這是一幅我們很喜愛的作品
and a prized possession.
非常感謝你們
Thank you all very much.
謝謝你們
Thank you.
因為那樣看上去就太清白了  好像我們...
Because it would've seemed too clean otherwise, like we were--
你讓我丟盡了臉
You made me look like an idiot.
如果我們說法一致
If we had the same story,
媒體會認為我們是串通好了
the media would assume we were coordinating.
必須亂一些
It needed to look messier.
這事本該結束的  克萊爾
This was supposed to go away, Claire.
但現在我樓外的記者多了一倍
I've got twice as much press outside the building now.
亞當
Adam...
我不得不把燈都關上
I've gotta keep the lights off
因為他們在對面樓頂上  想要拍我們
'cause they're on the roof across the street, trying to film us inside.
你只需要證實照片是你為我們拍攝的
You just need to confirm that you took the photo for us.
證實我們的說法
Confirm our version.
說你說謊是因為你害怕了
Say you lied because you were scared.
我不明白你為什麼不事先
I don't know why you didn't just tell me
把你要做的告訴我
this is what you were intending to do.
因為我瞭解你  你會拒絕的
Because I know you, and you would've refused.
你自尊心太強了
You have too much pride.
我不想再面對媒體了
I don't want to speak to the press again.
聽著
Listen.
如果你什麼都不說
If you say nothing,
他們不會放過你的
they're not going to leave you alone.
他們會在外面守上幾星期
They will just camp out for weeks on end--
這...我覺得這樣不對  克萊爾
This is... it feels wrong, Claire.
我覺得...
It feels...
抱歉我說謊了
I'm sorry I lied.
我並不是想擺佈你
I wasn't trying to be manipulative--
我要掛了
I have to go.
亞當
Adam?
我覺得他會想通的
I think he'll do the right thing.
不清楚  但願吧
I don't know. I hope so.
要來支煙嗎
Cigarette?
不用了  我去睡了
No. I'm gonna turn in.
他上電視了叫我
Wake me if he goes on TV.
-先生  -道格
- Sir. - Doug,
你和賽斯過來一下
why don't you and Seth come over?
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
要不要考慮起訴這家報紙
Should we consider a lawsuit against the paper?
表明我們不容忍這種八卦
Show we won't tolerate this sort of gossip?
他們不會和解的
They won't settle.
他們樂意上法庭  這樣能製造更多新聞
They'll fight it in the courts because it'll generate more news.
總統那兒呢
And what about the president?
他提出要表個態
He offered to say something.
這樣熱度就更高了
Draws more attention.
總統發話不是個壞主意
President isn't a bad idea,
只要我們幫他起草講話稿
if we phrase a statement for him.
如果他成了頭條新聞
He becomes the headline
我們控制不了他的媒體策略
and we can't control his press operation.
但如果我們和他們協調好  就不會...
But if we coordinate with them, it shouldn't --
協調會讓人生疑
Coordination looks bad.
所以你得讓人看不出痕跡啊
So it's your job to conceal it.
如果賽斯覺得總統的講話有弊無利
If Seth doesn't think the president should make a comment,
我們就相信他的判斷吧
then we should defer to his judgment.
我再去拿瓶啤酒
I'm gonna go get another beer.
-我幫你去拿吧  -不用  我正想活動下手腳
- I can go grab you one, sir. - No. I feel like stretching my legs.
道格  來罐健怡可樂
Doug, diet Coke?
不用了  謝謝  先生
I'm fine, thank you, sir.
賽斯  來瓶啤酒
Seth, a beer?
我還得開車  謝了
I have to drive, but thanks.
我去去就回
I'll be right back.
你給我小心點
Watch yourself.
什麼意思
What do you mean?
康納很容易扳倒
Connor was an easy target,
但我可不是
but I'm not going anywhere.
道格  能有這位置我已經很滿意了
Look, doug, I'm grateful just to be here.
我在副總統身邊這麼久
You think I've survived with the vice president
你這點小花招還看不出來
so long by being blind?
給他們工作的晉陞空間是有上限的
Upward mobility has a ceiling with the Underwoods.
我就是上限
I'm the ceiling.
懂了
Understood.
你手裏還有他們什麼把柄
What else have you got on them?
沒了
Nothing.
你交出日記的時候沒留一手嗎
You fork over the journal without a backup plan for a rainy day?
我不相信
I don't think so.
我有什麼牌就出什麼牌
I had one hand and I played it.
我不會冒險
I don't press my luck.
你不會指望我會相信吧
You can't expect me to believe you.
我沒指望
I don't.
換做我是你我也不相信
I wouldn't if I were you.
但我說的是實話
But I'm telling the truth.
兄弟間的小鬥爭不是什麼壞事
A little sibling rivalry isn't such a bad thing,
特別是在養子之間
especially between adopted boys.
他們要麼彼此施壓
They either push each other
兩人都更上一層樓
to be the best versions of themselves,
要麼其中一人被踢回孤兒院
or one of them gets booted back to the orphanage.
在我家  我喝你們也得喝
You're in my house. You drink if I drink.
你的健怡可樂  你的啤酒
One Diet Coke for you, and one beer for you.
謝謝  先生
Thank you, sir.
親愛的  真是一團糟
Oh, darling, what a mess.
親愛的
Sweetheart.
你們還撐得住嗎
How are you holding up?
媒體接連騷擾了我們兩天
The press have been harassing us the past two days.
我們好不容易離開公寓  差點被他們踩死
we barely made it out of the building without being trampled.
太可怕了
Oh, how awful.
你說這兒有人要見我
You said someone was here to see me?
他在我辦公室
He's in my office.
他告訴你他是誰了嗎
Did he tell you who he was?
我不想在電話裏說
I didn't want to say over the phone.
這世道什麼都說不准
You never know, these days.
他說他以前為安德伍德夫婦工作
He says he used to work for the Underwoods.
-是誰  -你的助理
- Who? - Your assistant.
-不  她不會...  -她會  她做了
- No, she would never-- - She would and she did.
你有什麼目的
Why are you doing this?
-不是我  是我的老闆  -那是誰
- Not me. The man I work for. - And who is that?
這與你無關
That doesn't concern you.
你是在攪和我的生活
This is my life you're fucking with.
你和我都只是小卒  嘉樂威先生
You and I are just pawns, Mr. Galloway.
你走吧
You should leave.
我們需要更多證據...
We need more...
證明這事發生過  再給我一張照片
...to prove the affair happened. Another photograph.
給你30秒  走出這扇門
Thirty seconds, you better be out the door.
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
認識這個國家區號嗎
You recognize the country code?
城市區號是波哥大的
And the city code is Bogota.
還沒人接聽嗎
Is it still ringing?
馬歇爾
Marshall!
老爹
Hey, pops.
老天  從沒見這裏這麼火
Man, never seen it like this before.
隊都排到街上了
The line's down the block.
挺壯觀  是吧
Something else, ain't it?
看來你需要人幫忙
Looks like you could use some help.
後廚還有條圍裙
Got a extra apron in the back.
幹活兒了
Let's go!
她賴在門廳不肯走
She refuses to leave the lobby.
她叫什麼
What's her name?
艾拉·薩伊德  《華爾街電訊報》的
Ayla Sayyad, Wall Street Telegraph.
她是副總統記者團的成員
She's part of the Vice President's press corps.
這樣啊
Oh, yeah.
叫她上來吧
Send her up.
多謝你了  特莉莎  我沒事
I appreciate it, tricia, but I'm fine.
這件事鬧個一兩天也就過去了
This whole thing will blow over in a day or so,
那時我再
and I'll...
你能稍等下嗎
Can you hold on one second?
《日報》來電  他們要你發表評論
The Daily. They called for a comment.
亞當和他們談過了嗎
Did Adam speak with them?
談過了  但不是按我們的要求說的
Yes, but not what we told him to say.
他把這個發給報社了
He sent them this.
特莉莎  我能過會兒再打給你嗎
Tricia, can I call you back?
-這是你嗎  -不是
- Is that you? - No.
但他說這就是你
Because he's saying it is.
-可能是  -安德伍德夫人
- It might be. - Mrs. Underwood.
有可能是  沒錯
I mean, it could be, yes.
應該是
It probably is.
我特地問過你還有沒有別的把柄
I asked you about any vulnerabilities.
我不知道他拍了這張
I didn't know he took this.
照片裏你留著短髮
You have short hair in the picture.
你說過戀情兩年前就斷了
You said it ended over two years ago.
我去年秋天去過他那兒
Well, I visited him last fall.
還有別人知道嗎  有誰在那兒見到過你嗎
Does anyone else know? Did anyone see you there?
他請朋友去過他的公寓
He had friends over, to his apartment.
我的天
Christ.
但我們說過他是位朋友了
But we've said that he's a friend.
我去拜訪他  參加聚會沒什麼問題
There's nothing wrong with me visiting him, being at a party.
等這照片上了《日報》的頭版就有問題了
There is if this photo is on the front page of the Daily.
在中國  政治和生意是糾纏不清的
Politics and business are intertwined in China,
想必你知道這一點
as I'm sure you know.
為了確保中央政府的許可
It's not uncommon to partner
結交有門路的合作夥伴很正常
with someone who can ensure Beijing's approval.
就是說你需要他的政治影響力
So you needed his political influence.
費盡心機  我們的合作還是泡湯了
All this is moot. Our venture fell through.
就在傑斐遜港大橋獲批之後
Right after the Port Jefferson Bridge was approved.
我和那項工程沒有任何關係
I had nothing to do with that project.
據我所知  馮也沒有
Neither did Feng, to my knowledge.
是沒有  但是吳彬陽投了資
No, but Wu Bin Yang did.
他是馮在北京的主要競爭對手
He's Feng's biggest rival in Beijing.
看來我沒資格給你上中國政治課了
It looks like I shouldn't be schooling you on Chinese politics.
你比我瞭解的多啊
You know far more than I.
你用了"糾纏不清"這個詞
You used the word "Intertwined."
這正是我對整件事的感受
That's the sense I'm getting from all of this.
核能補貼  中國精煉廠  大橋工程
The samarium subsidy, the Chinese refinery, the bridge,
以及你和總統的關係
your friendship with the President...
誰派你來的
Who sent you?
什麼派我來
Who sent me?
財富積累到我這種程度
When you're as rich as I am,
就總得提防明槍暗箭
you're always a target.
我自己找來的
Nobody sent me.
但是你坐在這兒
You're here...
在聖路易斯採訪
in St. Louis.
而不是去報道副總統夫婦的醜聞
Instead of covering the vice president and his wife.
我覺得馮山德背後還有更多隱情
My gut says there's more to Xander Feng than has been reported.
-是嗎  -把時間花在這上面
- Yeah. - It's a far better use of my time
比報道什麼八卦性醜聞更值得
than reporting on tabloid sex scandals.
那不是真正的新聞
It's not real news.
你懷念德黑蘭了吧
You miss Tehran.
你在下面等待時  我讀了幾篇你的文章
I read some of your work while you were in the waiting area.
-那裏越來越危險了  -可不是
- It started to get too dangerous. - Yeah.
那種環境不適合
Not the best place to be
結婚成家  生兒育女
when you want to get married and start a family.
或者猶太人
Or if you're Jewish.
也對
That, too.
我太太去那兒旅遊時給我買了這個回來
My wife got this for me when she visited there,
那是在伊斯蘭革命之前
before the revolution.
很漂亮
It's beautiful.
16世紀的古董
16th century.
托運回國的時候被弄碎了
It, um, broke when it was being shipped,
摔得粉碎
into a thousand pieces.
好幾名專家花了一年多才修復如初
It took specialists over a year to restore it.
給  我希望你能收下
Here, I want you to have it.
我不能接受你的禮物
I can't accept gifts.
不不  這不是禮物
No, no. Not as a gift.
只是給你提個醒
No. As a reminder of how hard it can be to
有些東西一旦碎了  再拼起來就難了
put something back together again once it's been crushed.
你要是想威脅我的話
If you're going to threaten me,
完全不用這麼兜圈子
you don't have to go to the trouble of veiling it.
我一般不接受記者採訪
I don't usually do interviews with reporters.
他們就是寄生蟲
They're parasites.
大都一心琢磨怎麼想辦法打擊我
Usually interested in just finding a way to knock me down a peg.
自然而然
Invariably,
他們寫的東西都不準確
what they write is inaccurate.
如果他們不如實寫
And when that happens,
我就不得不反擊了
I have no choice but to retaliate.
美國也可以像伊朗一樣危險  薩伊德小姐
America can be just as dangerous as Iran, ms. Sayyad.
謝謝你抽時間見我  塔斯克先生
Thank you for your time, mr. Tusk.
回華盛頓的路上注意安全
Travel safe back to Washington.
給雷米打電話
Get Remy on the line.
雷米在二線
Remy's on line two.
雷米
Remy.
我們不要再留後手了
Let's not hold back on the other thing.
再次打擊他  現在就執行
Hit 'em again, and hit 'em now.
收益最好的一天
Best day yet.
你得弄個保險箱什麼的
You gotta get a safe or something.
或者讓銀行上門收存款什麼的
Or maybe one of those, uh, pickup services.
晚上帶這麼多錢走路太危險了
That's too much money to be carrying around at night.
我自己能應付
I can handle myself.
你對著槍口還怎麼應付
There ain't nobody can handle a Glock to the face.
除非你自己有一把
Unless you got one yourself.
我早就不帶傢伙了
My days of packin' are long gone.
來
There.
拿我的
Take mine.
我家裏還有一把
I got one at home.
你把那東西帶到這裏來幹什麼
What the fuck you doin' bringin' that thing in here?
只是為了安全
Oh, it's just for protection, man.
我都不知道你為什麼要有槍
I don't know what you doing with it anyway.
你的假釋條例怎麼辦
What about your parole?
比起假釋官我更擔心
I'm a lot more worried about niggas in my building
我家樓裏的黑鬼們
than some parole officer.
好了  坐下
All right, sit down.
你瞧  我說的就是這個
See, man? This is what I'm talkin' about, man.
你自以為是地評價我
You being all righteous and judgin' me and shit.
給我個面子  坐下  快點
Do me a favor and just sit down. Sit down now.
聽著
Look.
我們可能遇到件好事
We got us a good thing, potentially.
可能最終沒有結果  也可能會有好結果
Maybe nothing comes of it, but maybe something does.
如果連鎖店成功
If the joint works out,
或許有一天你能當經理
maybe one day you could be the manager.
如果真的火起來
Shit, if it blows up,
你能去經營整個連鎖店
you could run the whole fucking franchise.
但那意味著你得小心點
But that means you gotta be careful.
你不能再被抓回去了
That means you cannot be sent back inside.
我們得遵紀守法
We gotta follow the rules.
聽懂了嗎
Hear me?
好吧
All right.
你會處理掉那東西嗎
You gonna get rid of that thing?
會的
Yeah.
那就好
All right.
這才像個男人
Now that's what's being a man.
我需要你剪短頭髮
I'll need you to cut it.
多短
How short?
這麼短
This short.
我還要做模特呢  如果我剪那麼短
I have a modeling career. If I cut it that short--
如果你真有模特工作
If you actually had a modeling career,
我就會在和你經紀人談
I would be speaking to your agency,
而不是坐在你的公寓裏
and not sitting in your apartment.
你到底想不想要這份工作
Do you want this job or not?
好吧
OK, yeah.
我可以剪短
I can cut it.
好的
All right.
在我們去攝影棚之前
And before we go to the studio,
我需要知道你是否口齒清楚
I need to see how well-spoken you are.
這有什麼關係
Why does that matter?
因為你會出現在全美所有的新聞頻道上
Because you're gonna be on every news channel in America.
等等  這是怎麼回事
Wait. What's this for?
讀出這個  一字不差
Read this. Those exact words.
讀出來
Read 'em.
如果你有本事  就該背出來
If you're good, you'll memorize them.
我的名字是斯特芬妮·道瑞
My name is Stephanie Daldry.
我是一名職業模特
I am a professional model.
弗萊迪·海耶斯因在哥倫比亞高地
Freddy Hayes was convicted in 1982
搶劫一家便利店  而於1982年被定罪
for sticking up a convenience store in Columbia Heights.
在高速追捕中
During a high-speed pursuit,
海耶斯失控撞向另一輛車
Hayes lost control and crashed into another vehicle,
導致一對老夫婦死亡
killing an elderly couple.
他承認犯有持械搶劫罪
He avoided manslaughter charges
以免受過失殺人的起訴
by pleading guilty to armed robbery.
他服刑九年
He served nine years.
1992年他開了弗萊迪燒烤餐館
In 1992 he opened Freddy's BBQ Joint,
一家專做肋排的小餐館
a small restaurant specializing in ribs,
副總統弗蘭克·安德伍德是那裏的常客
frequented by Vice President Frank Underwood.
你知道嗎
Did you know?
不  我不知道
No, I didn't.
你認為是塔斯克
You think it's Tusk?
還能是誰
Who else?
弗·安德伍德
你在給誰發短信
Who are you texting?
你在哪
賽斯
Seth.
你在哪
至賽斯·格雷森
賽斯·格雷森
攝影棚
弗·安德伍德
來我家
我想發佈一份簡短聲明
All I want to do is make a short statement.
弗萊迪已經服過刑了
Freddy did his time.
他20年來一直遵紀守法
He's been an upstanding citizen for 20 years.
他是個殺死兩位老人的罪犯
He's a convicted felon who killed two senior citizens.
是意外
By accident.
那並不是重點
Well, that's beside the point.
我不能不管他
I am not gonna hang him out to dry.
如果沒有嘉樂威的事
If the Galloway story wasn't happening,
我認為這可以
I'd say it's fine.
但現在太冒險了
But it's too risky right now.
想想這看起來像什麼樣
Think of how this is shaping up.
一個戴綠帽子
A vice president whose wife cheats on him
還和前罪犯做朋友的副總統
and who is friendly with a former gang-banger?
你維護他不會有好結果
There is no way you win standing up for this guy.
他馬上要開連鎖店了
He's about to start a franchise.
我不容許這事告吹
I will not have it jeopardized
就因為塔斯克決定針對...
because Tusk decides to come after --
這不單是弗萊迪的問題  先生
Is more than just Freddy, sir.
我做過調查
I did some digging.
他兒子因運毒和販毒坐過牢
His son did time for narcotics, trafficking, distribution--
我沒見過他兒子
I've never met his son.
這件事再緩緩  先解決
Let's hold off and tackle--
不  明早安排我跟記者見一下面
No. I want you to organize a press avail tomorrow morning.
派人接弗萊迪過來
Have Freddy brought over here.
從後門進
Bring him through the back.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
我不會對自己人見死不救
I won't leave one of my own bleeding on the field.
如果是華盛頓紅人隊
If you're gonna have the Washington Redskins,
那對手必須是紐約尼克斯隊
then you're gonna have to have the New York Knickers.
華盛頓紅人是美式足球隊  紐約尼克斯是籃球隊
老爸  你完全弄錯了
Pops, you ain't even deep like that.
走開  夥計
Yo, back off, man.
都他媽滾開
Back the fuck off.
達奈爾  別理他們就好
Darnell, just ignore them.
你當我在開玩笑嗎
You think I'm fucking around?
達奈爾  別理他們
Darnell, ignore them! Ignore 'em.
我們不想被拍  他們就不能拍
They can't take our pictures if we don't want them to.
老子當然能
Sure as hell can.
你說什麼
What you say?
美國憲法第一修正案保護新聞自由
第一修正案
The First fuckin' Amendment.
你他媽要給我講憲法嗎
You gonna read me the constitution now, motherfucker?
行了  達奈爾  我們進去吧
Come on, Darnell. Let's just go on inside.
不行  我和這混蛋還沒完
Nah, nah, I ain't done with this asshole.
別碰我
Hey, don't touch me.
你能威脅我
But you can get all up in my face
我卻不能威脅你嗎
but I can't get up in yours?
-聽你爸的  冷靜點  -達奈爾  我們走吧
- Listen to your daddy and chill out. - Darnell, let's go.
別逼我
Don't push me.
小心我揍你
I will fuck you up.
你以為我怕你嗎
You think I'm scared of you?
怕這個嗎
You scared of this?
達奈爾  你的保釋
Darnell! Parole!
能告訴我你的名字嗎
Can you tell me your name, please?
斯特芬妮·道瑞
模特
Stephanie Daldry.
我是一名職業模特
I'm a professional model.
右邊照片裏的人是你嗎
And this is you in this photo on the right?
實拍還是造假
安德伍德照片真實性遭質疑
沒錯
Yes, that's correct.
道瑞小姐的這張照是昨天拍的
We shot this photo yesterday with Ms. Daldry.
你是說嘉樂威先生的照片是假的嗎
So you're suggesting that Mr. Galloway's photo is a fake?
我對專業攝影一無所知
I don't know anything about professional photography,
賽斯·格雷森
副總統新聞發言人
我只是個做宣傳的
I'm just a flack.
但如果我們都能在24小時內偽造照片
But if we can create a fake in less than 24 hours,
像亞當·嘉樂威那樣的專業攝影師...
I think an expert photographer like Adam Galloway--
這指控相當嚴重
Those are serious allegations,
特別是在嘉樂威先生極力否認的情況下
especially given that Mr. Galloway vehemently denies it.
我對他的否認並不意外
I'm not surprised he's denying.
不過最後就是你們兩人對質了
Ultimately, though, it's gonna be your word against his.
不是我
Not my word.
是美國的副總統
The vice president of the United States'.
他和一個可能有問題的人的對質
It's his word versus that of a potentially troubled man.
有問題
Troubled?
可能
Potentially.
或許他是有動機的
Or maybe he has a motive.
嘉樂威先生會有什麼造假的動機呢
What motive could Mr. Galloway possibly have for a fake photo?
他能從中得到什麼
What would he get out of it?
我不知道
I don't know.
我的工作是區分事實和虛構
My job is to separate fact from fiction,
這點和你一樣  坎迪
just like yours is, Candy.
但或許對搞藝術的人來說
But maybe fact and fiction
事實和虛構不那麼重要
don't matter as much to the artistic sensibility.
或許他分得不那麼清楚
Maybe the lines are blurred for him.
他並不拍攝虛構的作品
This is not a man who stages fictitious scenarios.
剛才也說了  我不懂藝術
Like I said, the art stuff, it's over my head.
或許你是對的
And you may be right.
但我不願相信
But I would hate to think
嘉樂威先生這麼做僅僅是為了炒作
that Mr. Galloway was doing this just for publicity.
你認為這是炒作
You think it's a publicity stunt.
進來
Come on in.
先生
Sir?
弗萊迪在路上了嗎
Is Freddy on his way?
他兒子出事了
There was an incident with his son.
發生了什麼
What happened?
他因持槍威脅攝像師被警方拘留
He's in custody for threatening a photographer with a firearm.
上帝啊
Jesus.
弗萊迪現在在哪
Where is Freddy now?
他在家
He's at home.
我得去看他
I have to go see him.
那裏是貧困住宅區
That's the projects, sir.
我不管  你看著辦
I don't care, you figure it out,
而且不能讓媒體知道
and the press can't know.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
弗蘭西斯  我也很喜歡弗萊迪
Francis, you know I love Freddy...
我一定要去
I'm going.
弗萊迪有危險  是因為你太在乎他
Freddy is dangerous because you care too much.
太過在乎  會使人盲目
When we care too much, it blinds us.
塔斯克的做法太卑鄙了
What Tusk did is cheap.
但你卻讓這事影響到你  這正是他的目的
And you're letting it get to you, which is exactly what he wants.
如果我視而不見  無所作為
If I ignore this, if I do nothing--
這不是無所作為
It's not nothing.
保持專注也需要力量
Staying focused requires strength.
要我給你做點什麼嗎
You want me to make something?
你吃吧  我不餓
You go ahead. I'm not hungry.
你得吃點
You should eat.
對不起  這本來跟你無關
I'm sorry. You didn't ask for this.
這對你不公平
It's not fair to you.
我只想快點結束
All I want is to be done with it.
讓我父親平安
For my father to be all right.
如果我當時還有別的辦法...
If I thought there was any other way, that...
我不想冒險讓他...
I didn't want to take the chance that he would--
我知道
I know.
這些人
These people.
我一向知道他們很無情  但是
I always knew they were ruthless, but...
我們像動物一樣關在這裏
We're caged up in here like animals.
他們把我刻畫成了那種...
They're painting me as some sort of...
還有你的家人
And your family...
太殘忍了
It's inhuman.
他們太他媽殘忍了
They're fucking inhuman.
生氣也不能改變局面
Getting worked up isn't going to change anything.
我來
Let me.
你好
Hello?
弗蘭克
Hey, Frank.
可以了
I'm fine.
謝謝你來看我
Thanks for dropping by.
你還好嗎
How you holdin' up?
湊合吧
I been better.
從沒見過你不穿西裝的樣子
Ain't never seen you without a suit before.
我們不想太招人注意
We didn't want to draw too much attention.
就是這樣  我的城堡
Well, this is it, my castle.
不如你的大  但也夠用了
Ain't as big as yours, but it'll do the job.
盲眼威利Blind Willie.
盲眼威利·約翰遜  美國福音藍調歌手  吉他演奏家
你喜歡藍調嗎
Are you a blues fan?
《漆黑的夜晚》  每次聽都讓我陶醉
"Dark Was the Night." Gets me every time.
夥計  你早該告訴我
Man, you shoulda told me that years ago.
我會即興演奏  聊起藍調能聊一整天
I can jam, talking about some blues all day long.
看看這張  78年原版
Check this out. Original 78.
要喝點什麼嗎
You want something?
水  還是冰茶
Water? Iced tea?
我想要冰茶  謝謝
I'd like some iced tea, thank you.
你兒子怎麼樣了
How's your son?
他們要六萬保釋金
They set the bail at 60 grand.
天哪
Jesus.
你妻子怎麼樣了
How's your wife doing?
克萊爾有一副三英吋厚的鎧甲
Oh, Claire's got a suit of armor three inches thick.
這些難關我們會撐過去的
We'll get through all this garbage.
有人想毀了你嗎
Somebody's tryin' to take you out?
看來是的
Appears that way.
無論是誰
Whoever it is,
他們踩到不該踩的響尾蛇了
they done stepped on the wrong motherfuckin' rattlesnake.
所以我來這裏了  弗萊迪
That's why I'm here, Freddy.
我得遠離你
I have to distance myself from you.
我要確保你不會到處宣揚
I need to make sure you're not going to play up
我們是多好的朋友
what good friends we've been.
說你去過我的辦公室
That you've been to my office,
還曾在我家做晚餐
that you've cooked dinner at my home,
而且總統也出席了那次晚餐
or that the president was there.
我們不能連累了他
We can't drag him into anything.
我再也不會來吃肋排了
And I won't be coming in for ribs anymore.
現在出了這麼多事
With all that's going on,
我們不能再火上澆油了
we can't add fuel to the fire.
你就是想來吃也吃不到了
You couldn't if you wanted to.
我要賣掉了
I'm selling it.
賣掉餐館嗎
Selling the Joint?
沒錯
That's right.
你在說什麼呢
What are you talking about?
醬汁的特許經營權什麼的
The franchise thing, with the sauce.
我的生意夥伴要解約了
My business partner's pullin' out.
說他們銀泉的白人不喜歡去
Say them white folks down in Silver Spring don't wanna
惡棍開的餐館
go to no place run by thugs.
那你為什麼非得賣掉你的店
Why do you have to sell yours?
達奈爾的保釋金
Darnell's bail.
那傢伙不是無論如何都得給你十萬美金嗎
Doesn't that guy have to give you a hundred grand, regardless?
我屁都拿不到
I ain't getting shit.
合同里有一條道德條款
There's a morality clause in the contract.
但他打算花四萬五買我的門面
But he's gonna pay me 45 thou for the storefront.
再加上我存的一點錢  就可以付保釋金了
That with what little I got saved, I can pay that bond.
你不能把餐館賣掉
You can't sell Freddy's.
他已經在起草合同了
He's already drawing up the papers.
我來幫你解決錢的問題
Let me help you with the money.
不用  弗蘭克
Nah, Frank.
就當做是借貸
We'll make it a loan.
你可以以後再還我
You can pay me back.
不行
Not gonna happen.
別要強
Don't be prideful.
-弗蘭克  -拜託  讓我幫你吧
- Frank. - Please, let me help.
你這是內疚  我不會要的
I ain't takin' your guilt money.
過去在道上的時候
When I was bangin',
我們一個月能賺六萬美金
we used to clear 60 Gs a month.
我見過同伴被人殘忍槍殺
I seen guys shot down execution-style.
但我一點也不關心
I didn't give a shit.
之後我被捕了
Then I got caught.
坐牢的第一年裏達奈爾出生了
Darnell was born my first year in.
我一次也沒見過他  連照片都沒有
Never saw him once, not even a picture.
我不能收回我所犯的罪惡
I can't take back the bad I done.
我所能做的就是一如既往
All I can do is to make my own way,
自己想辦法活下去  你明白嗎
like I've been doing. You understand?
不是要強  弗蘭克
Ain't pride, Frank.
如果你改變心意了  就告訴我
If you change your mind, you let me know.
你是一個好顧客  僅此而已
You was a good customer, that's it.
你不必假裝是我的朋友
You ain't gotta pretend to be my friend.
多多保重  弗萊迪
You take care of yourself, Freddy.
你也是  弗蘭克
You too, Frank.
你覺得我是一個偽君子嗎
Do you think I'm a hypocrite?
那就對了
Well, you should.
我不會否認
I wouldn't disagree with you.
通向權利的道路由虛偽
The road to power is paved with hypocrisy...
和犧牲鋪就
...and casualties.
永遠不要後悔
Never regret.
這邊請
This way.
請坐  亞當
Have a seat, Adam.
你按要求的那樣  把電話留在家裏了嗎
You left your phone at home, as you were asked?
是的
Yeah.
你是怎麼跟你未婚妻說的
And what did you tell your fiancee exactly?
就說我要離開一陣子
That I'd be gone for a while.
她不知道我要去哪
She doesn't know where.
如果有人找到她  她會說什麼
And what will she say if someone checks in on her?
這是幹什麼
What is this?
她會說什麼
What will she say?
弗蘭西斯
Francis.
我們現在得協調合作
We need to work together now.
我試過  但你騙了我
I tried. You lied to me.
而我也解釋了為什麼要那麼做
And I explained to you why that was necessary.
可你不聽我的命令
You didn't follow my instructions.
你們知道雷米·丹頓是誰嗎
Do you know who Remy Danton is?
他找過你嗎
He approached you?
伊奈茲的父親是波哥大的一位人權運動家
Inez's father is a human rights activist in Bogota.
政府說他勾結叛亂分子
The government has charged him with treason
控告他叛國
for working with the rebels.
他們要判他死刑
They're going for the death penalty,
丹頓說他們可以操縱法官
and Danton said they have the judge in their pocket.
你應該來找我們
You should have come to us.
我跟他說了
I said I would.
丹頓說你什麼也做不了
Danton said you couldn't do anything.
他錯了
He's wrong.
我不能冒險
I wasn't gonna take any chances.
她父親如政府所稱那樣犯罪了嗎
Has he done what the government's claiming?
沒有  都是些無中生有的指控
No. They're made-up charges.
他只是一個記者
He's a journalist
報道達恩地塹那裏的殘暴行徑
documenting atrocities in the Darien Gap.
巴拿馬與哥倫比亞之間未開發的大片沼澤地
我可以撤銷指控
I can get the charges dropped.
我憑什麼相信你
Why should I trust you?
因為國務卿是我的好朋友
Because the secretary of state is a good friend of mine.
而且你別無選擇
And you don't have any other choice.
我們不是你的棋子
We're not your chess pieces.
這也不是遊戲  嘉樂威先生
And this isn't a game, Mr. Galloway.
那你為什麼要耍我們
Then why are you toying with us?
我們只是想幫你
We are trying to help.
開什麼玩笑  克萊爾
That's a fucking joke, Claire.
不准這樣和我妻子說話
Do not talk to my wife that way.
你妻子  那對你來說有什麼意義
Your wife. What does that even mean to you?
別因為你們之間有過一段歷史
Do not mistake any history you have shared
就以為你瞭解我們的婚姻
for the slightest understanding of what our marriage is
相比之下  你完全無關緊要
or how insignificant you are in comparison.
能讓我倆單獨談談嗎
Can you give us a few minutes?
我去給凱茜打電話
I'm gonna go call Cathy.
不說我的事業和名聲吧
Forget my career and my reputation.
我想和這個女人結婚  克萊爾
I want to marry this woman, Claire.
我們會擺平這件事的
We're going to make this disappear.
因為你  我將永遠是那個
Because of you I will always be the man
將她父親置於險境的人
who placed her father in danger.
這永遠無法抹去
I can never erase that.
很遺憾事情走到了這個地步
I'm sorry it's come to this.
我真後悔遇見你
I'm sorry I ever met you.
從頭到尾  你只給過我痛苦
All you've ever done is cause me pain.
現在你又來破壞我的生活
Now you're fucking with my life
還有我未婚妻的生活
and the life of the woman
我愛她遠勝過愛你
that I love more than I ever loved you.
你今晚就開車回紐約
You'll be driven back to New York tonight.
明天一早  你就發表聲明
In the morning, you'll make a statement saying
說這是炒作
this was a publicity stunt,
你的作品一直賣不出好價錢
and that the value of your work had been stagnating
-所以你希望重振...  -不  克萊爾
- and you wanted to revive - No, Claire.
-我才不會那樣做  -你會的
- I won't do that. - Yes, you will.
不如我去告訴記者
How about I tell the press,
-我被帶到這兒來  -亞當  閉嘴
- that you, that I was brought here - Adam, shut up!
你要說你想博取關注  然後又害怕了
That you wanted the attention, then you got cold feet,
否認了照片的事  接著又再次改了主意
denied it, then you changed your mind again.
那張浴室照片是你偽造的
And that you faked the shower photo
你要澄清這一點
and you're coming clean.
明白了嗎
Is that clear?
我不該被捲進這種事中
I'm not part of this world.
我沒想攪進來  我也不感興趣
I didn't sign up for it. I have no interest in it.
我們給你提供了一條出路  亞當
We're giving you an out, Adam.
如果你選擇不接受的話
And if you choose not to take it,
我會毀掉你
I will bury you.
我從沒恨過任何人
I've never hated anyone before.
現在我知道那是什麼感覺了
Now I know what that feels like.
感覺很糟  對嗎
It's a terrible feeling, isn't it?
終止呼叫
End call.
呼叫已終止
Call ended.
呼叫雷蒙德·塔斯克
Call Raymond Tusk.
他的住處沒人接電話
No answer at his place.
是想要更多錢嗎
Is it a matter of more money?
國務卿杜蘭特已經致電莫裏諾總統
Secretary Durant has already called President Moreno.
那我們得趕快行動了
So we need to move quickly.
外交部長已經牽扯進來了
The minister of foreign affairs is involved now.
法官不會在12小時內就宣判他有罪
The judge isn't gonna rush a conviction in less than 12 hours.
我們認識什麼能跟部長說上話的人嗎
Who do we know who has the minister's ear?
沒有人能夠比得過莫裏諾總統
Nobody who can trump President Moreno.
而他對杜蘭特對人權方面的看法非常敏感
And he's very sensitive to Durant's view on human rights.
你是打算放棄了嗎
Are you giving up on this?
不  只是現實一點
No. Just being realistic.
那就做莫裏諾的工作
Work on Moreno then.
我們快要被人察覺了
We'll start leaving footprints.
安靜點
Quiet.
你說什麼
Excuse me?
不是說你  是我的鳥
Oh, not you. My birds.
我覺得我們要做好準備
I think we need to be prepared
我們很可能沒法把威脅進行到底了
for the possibility that we can't follow through with our threat.
我聽到的都是借口  不是解決方案
I am hearing excuses, not solutions.
我無能為力
My hands are tied.
我沒法搞定整個美國國務院
I can't circumvent the entire US State Department.
我雇你是為了讓你毀掉弗蘭克
You know, I hired you to destroy Frank.
你要失敗了
You're failing.
雷蒙德  我是你的說客
Look, Raymond, I'm your lobbyist,
不是你的走狗
not your henchman.
我雇的不是說客
I don't employ lobbyists.
我雇的是對我有用的人
I employ people who can be useful to me.
而你看起來沒用
And you are proving otherwise.
安靜點
Quiet now.
我會想辦法的
I'll figure something out.
快點
Soon.
行  就這樣
Okay, that's good.
你不必這麼做
You don't have to do this.
不  我必須這麼做
Yeah, I do.
指控撤銷了
The charges are dropped.
他們騙了你
They lied to you.
你也可以騙他們
You can lie to them.
還可以提出新指控
New charges can always be filed.
不能冒這個險
It's not worth the risk.
好吧
Ok.
你對我感到失望嗎
Are you disappointed in me?
趕緊把這事弄完吧
Let's just get it over with.
好吧  開始
OK, go ahead.
我要做出一項聲明
I'd like to make a statement.
還需要一些掃尾工作
There will be a little cleanup,
會有一些人繼續關注這件事
some folks who will want to linger on the story,
但我們已經渡過最困難的階段了
but we're over the hump, I'd say.
那我們現在可以出門了嗎
So we can leave the house now?
越快恢復正常工作越好
The sooner you get back to normal work, the better.
之前被迫取消的會議
All the meetings I had to cancel,
想辦法再做安排
let's find a way to get them back on the books.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
我得繼續推動性侵法案
I need to push ahead with the Assault Bill.
我們安排了明天和馬特·貝的採訪
We've got your Matt Bai interview lined up for tomorrow,
但我認為...
but I think that--
也許我們應該等事情平息之後
Maybe we should hold off on Bai
再考慮貝的採訪
till after things quiet down.
我剛才正打算這麼說
That's exactly what I was gonna suggest.
道格說得對
Doug is right.
好  就這麼辦
OK, let's get going.
我在車裏等你
I'll meet you in the car.
他這些事處理得很好
He's done a good job handling all this.
是的
Yes, he has.
那我們還要擔心什麼嗎
Should we have any more concerns?
他說他沒有別的把柄了
He claims he doesn't have anything else.
你相信他嗎
Do you believe him?
還沒到那個地步
I wouldn't go that far.
盯著他點
Keep an eye on him.
正有此意
I plan to.
至於雷蒙德  我們快速有力地回擊
As for Raymond, we have to strike back hard and fast.
我要打垮他
I want him obliterated.
還不夠
More than that.
讓他受點折磨吧
Let's make him suffer.
真不知我是該驕傲還是害怕
I don't know whether to be proud or terrified.
也許兩者皆有
Perhaps both.
真希望我能多給你一些
Wish I could do more.
你打算拿她做什麼
What you gonna do with her?
還沒想好
I don't know yet.
也許要把它拆掉
Probably have to knock it down.
空地價值更高
It's worth more as an empty lot.
你還有別的東西想拿走嗎
Is there anything else you wanna take?
紀念品之類的
A memento or something?
沒了
Nah.
我不是一個向後看的人
I ain't one for lookin' back.
我只向前看
Eyes ahead.
祝你好運  弗萊迪
Good luck, Freddy.
在這一集中  弗萊迪意外成了白宮爭鬥中的一枚棋子
在現實生活中  美國一些不知名的街邊小店
也經常迎來總統和議員們的光顧
2012年的總統大選開始後  奧巴馬幾乎每到一地競選
都會在百忙中抽時間到當地聞名的餐館食坊"嘗嘗鮮"
新罕布什爾"牛奶吧"的冰激凌  科羅拉多"辛克餐廳"的披薩
愛荷華州"羅斯餐館"的"魔山三明治"  都被奧巴馬嘗了個遍
他一邊走馬燈似的拉票  一邊扮演業餘美食家
身邊的記者們也都盡職盡責地
把總統在各地小吃  餐館中"大快朵頤"的照片傳給了全美選民
一次奧巴馬在競選途中"突襲"佛羅里達的"大蘋果披薩"
店主興奮不已  打招呼時給了奧巴馬一個"熊抱"
總統被身高2米  體重兩百多斤的披薩店老闆"拔地而起"的照片
成了2012年大選中最為經典  傳播最廣的一張照片
美國政客的一舉一動都處於媒體的聚光燈下
當下美國的政黨選舉和黨派鬥爭
已經不再只是不同的意識形態和政治立場間的較量
更是一場耗資巨大  無所不用其極的"公關秀"
"做得好"不如"演得好"
美國政壇中的各路人馬無不挖空心思拉近同選民的距離
民以食為天
食物自然也成了每天上演的各檔政治秀中的一個重要角色
不過政客們不是美食家
他們吃著嘴裏的  惦記的卻是選民兜裏的選票